#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mohit-s0631 (LinkedIn) mohits0631.myportfolio.com/ (Portfolio)

#### Top Skills

C++

C (Programming Language)
Python (Programming Language)

### Languages

French (Elementary)
English (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

Introduction to CSS3

Technology Consulting Virtual Internship

Software Engineering Virtual Experience

Introduction to HTML5

Interactivity with JavaScript

# Mohit Singh

Web Designer and Developer | Technology Consultant virtual intern at Deloitte | TEDxNITRaipur

Raipur

# Summary

I am an experienced executive with a demonstrated history of working in the non-profit organization management industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), C++, Communication, Graphic Design, and English and technologies such as Html, CSS, Javascript, and Sass.

A strong business development professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Chemical Engineering from the National Institute of Technology Raipur.

## Experience

TEDx NIT Raipur

8 months

Web Designer May 2020 - Present (4 months)

Design Executive January 2020 - May 2020 (5 months) Chattisgarh, India

## PrepBytes

Campus Business Manager July 2020 - Present (2 months)

#### Deloitte

Technology Consulting Virtual Intern June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)

## Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Chemical Engineering (2019 - 2023)